Your last cover was gorgeous, Yachiyo.
Ever since she signed with that modeling group,
Yachiyo's career's been on fire.
Whatever happened to the others?
Who cares?
She's the last girl standing now.
Hard work only takes you so far in this business.
Without talent, you're nowhere.
That's cool.
I'm right, though.
I made a wish to survive in this industry.
That wish caused all my friends to vanish.
I caused it.
So I swore I'd never get close to anyone again.
Iroha, where are you?
Remember?
You promised me that you'd stay with me.
Iroha Tamaki is dead and gone like all the others.
You're wasting your time searching for her.
She's gone.
Forever.
Shut up!
Tell me where Magia's HQ is now.
The Uwasa are getting stronger and stronger.
They don't drop Graveseeds, so I can't purify my Soul Gem.
It's getting even cloudier.
Hotel Fent Hope, a mobile Uwasa barrier.
You told me before how whoever stays with you ends up dying, but I'm gonna prove you're wrong about that.
You liar!
Liar! Liar! Liar! Liar! Liar!
Mal...Kanai...
I will destroy the Magius.
The Magius will save everyone, so don't fret. We discovered a way to free all magical girls from our horrible fate.
They can save us from being witches? That's hard to believe.
Oh, don't be so negative. Have a little faith.
Do you think what she's saying is possible?
Mm-hmm. Without my doppel, I'd be a witch now. Remember?
It's too bad!
Heck, as long as all the witches are gone, I don't care how she does it.
Why don't you look happy about that?
I'm thrilled about it. It's just...
Just what?
I'm kind of worried about Iroha and her friends.
Yes, they're fine. Yachiyo's with them.
These girls have a plan, and if it really works, no one's ever gonna turn into a witch again.
Not you, Iroha, Yachiyo, or Tsuruno. If they can save us, I'm down for whatever.
Yeah...
We're super excited to share the final stage of our plan with you! It'll be soon, I promise! Till then, keep up the great work!
Remember, whether we succeed or fail depends on you!
That speech was fantastic! Everyone loved it!
I'll say. Your words were riveting, enchanting, inspiring!
Yeah, I know. Is there anything to report?
The Uwasa of Peking Castle Town, the Fireman's Mound, and Switch Street have all been defeated. And Yachiyo Nanami is the one responsible.
Ugh, good grief. Her again?
We know it's a huge loss for us, so we're having the other Uwasa catch more people to make up for it!
We can't let anything or anyone get in the way! You got it?
No! I mean yes!
I mean yes! We got it!
Our plan's almost ready, and we're not changing the date.
That means, till while Pergusnacht comes, we can't afford to make any more mistakes!
You understand that too, Mifuyu?
Yes. I won't fail the Magias.
Sorry. Kuroe, was it? I need your help with something. I'm Nemu Hiragi. I'm a leader of the Magias, but I don't think we've met before. We haven't. Um, what is it you wanted? I made a rumor, and I was hoping you could go out and find it.
Sorry, you... you said you made a rumor?
Yes. I made all the rumors in Pamehama City. Unfortunately, I used too much of my power making them. It took its toll and then some. I'm going to die soon as a result.
But never mind that. What I need is for you to go and find the rumor of the Eternal Sakura.
Rumor of the Eternal Sakura?
Yes. There's a special someone I want you to protect. I've written all the details down for you.
Wait! Are you sure? I don't know if I can handle this!
If I was well enough to do it myself, I would.
One more thing. Please keep this between you and me. It's very important you don't tell anyone.
If that's what you want. I mean it. Not even a member of the Magias. You can't tell anyone, no matter what.
Okay, I won't.
At this rate, I'm never gonna find it. This sucks. I should've said no to her.
It's that little teeny cubee.
Come back!
At last, I'm home.
What a day! I'm gonna kick back and veg out.
What the?
I let myself in, Mitama. I hope I didn't startle you too much.
Not at all. It's great to see you again.
You've been gone for quite a while. I started to think your shop was closed for good.
No, the shop's doing fine. I just had to take a little business trip is all.
That's just what I wanted to talk about.
Did you go see the Magias?
I met a girl who said she created the Doppels.
Yes, that girl would be Toka.
You lied. You didn't tell us you were adjusting our soul gems to help make Doppels for her cult.
Technically, I wasn't lying. I just left that little detail out is all.
In the end, I don't know what her ultimate goal is. I just put everyone's soul gems in alignment to help keep their Doppels in check.
You always said that even knowing about Doppels and their power was dangerous.
But the Magias say Doppels can be used somehow to free magical girls from their fate. Can they?
Officially, they're called Doppel Witches. They're a reflection of emotions.
When a soul gem gets so tainted, it becomes totally cloudy. The curse manifests in a section of the body.
It's the power of the witch, and it's what you use to make a Doppel.
When a Doppel Witch is summoned, the taint is removed from the soul gem during the transformation.
As a result, your gem gets purified without having to use a grief seed. This process makes it possible to avoid turning into a witch.
Sounds great if that's all you know about it, but Doppels are super addictive and they have bad side effects.
Their existence is connected with the truth about how magical girls become witches.
That's why I've always said it's dangerous to spread knowledge about them.
And yet, the Magias don't think so.
Well, maybe they think that compared to the risks, it's better than becoming a witch.
I don't have an opinion either way.
In my dealings with them, I've always tried to keep myself neutral.
I need to find their base. Do you know where Hotel Fent Hope is?
Like I said, I'm neutral and I'm staying that way. They're just trying to save magical girls. That's not such a bad thing, is it?
They've also killed magical girls. They must be stopped.
Now that Iroh has gone, I should feel pain, but I don't. I feel nothing. Just like before, when all my friends vanished. They were gone and life went on for me as usual. It was my fault it happened. I shouldn't have let it happen. And I hate myself for it. I know.
Where is their base?
I really don't know. Every time I've gone, I always had to have an invitation. The location always changes. You have to be guided there by a member of Magias. Someone wearing their symbol.
That's easy enough. That's easy enough. I'll just find a black feather and force them. I will destroy the Magias for what they're doing. Maybe then I'll find peace.
I've run out of grief seeds. I'd like to buy some.
That I can do.
An Uasa is definitely around here.
It's Cube! Why are you here?
Geez. About time you stopped.
Do I… know you?
Magias.
Yes.
Stop!
Why is that small Kyuubei with her?
That's it.
I saw you with Iroha in that Kyuubei.
You're the magical girl from Takarazaki.
I have some questions for you.
Go easy on her, Yachan.
If you come at her looking all scary, she's not going to talk to you.
Mifuyu!
It's good to see you again, Yachan.
How dare you show your face to me? Are you insane?
I didn't come here to pick a fight with you. I just want to talk.
I have nothing to say!
Look, I know the Magias can be a little rough sometimes.
But whatever sacrifices are made, we're just trying to save magical girls.
Don't lie!
You sacrificed one to save another.
You decided to sacrifice Iroha!
No, it wasn't like that.
We didn't know that would happen. It was an accident.
You expect me to believe that?
Please listen to me.
If the Magias' plan works, it'll save us from turning into witches.
Then weak magical girls like me and Iroha wouldn't have to die!
She's not dead!
She promised me she wouldn't die.
Is she dead?
Well, is she?
Calm down, please.
If she's dead, it's because of my wish.
I let it happen again.
But you made it happen!
I'll make you pay.
I'll make you all pay.
The Magias!
And you!
We're not enemies.
Why can't you understand that?
Hey, Kyu-Bay.
He tricked us into this life.
He didn't tell us how horrible it would be or how we'd all end up.
We won't abandon our fellow magical girls to their fate.
The wings of the Magias just want us to be free.
That's all we want.
We've been tricked and exploited.
Our wish is used against us.
All we do is suffer and end up losing everything.
Her doppel.
Bro!
The members of the wings of the Magius aren't strong like you.
So what?
They're all just weak, magical girls.
Like me, and like Iroha.
Don't you dare compare yourself to Iroha.
We're all the same.
We're weak and scared of losing everything because of a lie.
Shut your mouth.
All you're doing is talking about yourself.
Iroha is nothing like you.
She only cares about others.
My wish took her away.
She'd be here if it weren't for me.
You're wrong.
She's not like you.
She's not like you at all!
She's not like you at all.
Goodbye, Mifuil.
You're so weak.
It hurts to even look at you.
you're a victim because you're weak
you lose because you're weak
you suffer because you're weak
you're helpless because you're weak
goodbye
poor little weak
no
what am I doing
this isn't right
I don't want to kill you
no
that's not me
whatever my fate as a magical girl is
I accept it
but I won't let others die to change it
that's what I meant
when I said you were strong
but that's not me
Ya-chan
Mifu-ya
hey
oh great
wait for me
the labyrinth
hey
stop
I found it
what the
one day
the three girls will leave the hospital
and beneath a huge
wilted cherry tree
they'll be reunited with the older girl
who always came to visit them
then cherry blossoms will bloom gloriously on the tree
as if giving its blessing to their reunion
and the blossoms will never fall again
no matter how lost we feel
or how disillusioned we get
there will come a day
when we'll reach that tree
I'm going to call this one
the rumor of the eternal Sakura
Iroha
Irohou